http://www.totaldecorstore.com/page/privacy-policy-6

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is for Total Decor Store, Inc and customers with whom we do ecommerce business. As you use our shopping cart, you will notice we do NOT begin by asking you for your personal information. We designed the cart to keep you fully informed every step of the way and allow you to fully review your order including all shipping charges and tax, if any, before we ever ask for your personal information or to commit to the order. You have our promise, your personal information will NEVER be sold or revealed to another entity. Neither will we ever use it to solicit or spam you. It is used to conclude your purchase and that is all. We will honor your privacy.
Security Protection
We have appropriate physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards in place to secure the information we collect to do e-commerce business. In addition our web site uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal information including your credit card number before it travels over the internet. SSL is the industry standard for secure online transactions. By using SSL, we make placing an order online at our web site just as secure safe as giving your credit card number over the phone.
Safe Shopping Guarantee
We guarantee that every transaction you make with totaldecorstore.com will be protected, safe and secure. In the unlikely event an unauthorized charge is made to your card as a result of shopping with totaldecorstore.com, you will pay nothing.
Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank can not hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you responsible for any of this $50., totaldecorstore.com will cover the liability only if the unauthorized use of your card results through no fault of your own from purchases made at totaldecorstore.com while using our secure server.
Notification
In the event unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. Any material changes to this privacy policy will be posted on the web site and communicated via e-mail.
Total Decor Store
Home
About Us
Track Order
Wish List
Site Map
Blog
Customer Support
7714B N Hwy 146 #210,
Baytown,
Texas
77523,
USA
281-397-3971
sales@decormail.com
©
2010 - 2020 Total Decor Store. All Rights Reserved.
